GRISINGER USER INTERFACE DEVELOPER

CONTACT

303.884.4919



brett.grisinger@gmail.com



http://brettgrisinger.com

INTRO

I'm a well-versed user interface and interaction developer with over 10 years of professional experience and a passion for creating meaningful web applications by continually using the latest web technologies, methodologies and frameworks to deliver the most rewarding and engaging interactive experiences.

EXPERIENCE

STARZ ENTERTAINMENT // SENIOR INTERACTIVE DEVELOPER (09.2010 - PRESENT)

Support television original programming and affiliate sales through user interface and interactive development on microsites, press kits, games, social media campaigns and media buys. Develop web applications using ReactJS/Redux and SASS with a gulp workflow. Lead and mentor junior developers.

FACTION MEDIA // INTERACTIVE DEVELOPER (09.2009 - 09.2010)

Developed the front end of several client websites and interactive modules and worked with the back end team on implementation. Developed JQuery plugins, video players and other custom elements.

NATIONAL CINEMEDIA // INTERACTIVE DEVELOPER (06.2009 - 09.2009)

Front end development on ncm.com, fathomevents.com and other microsites using HTML, CSS and JQuery/JavaScript. Worked with UX team to prototype an interactive video editor.

ON TARGET JOBS // WEB DEVELOPER (01.2009 - 05.2009)

Front end development using HTML, CSS and JavaScript to build out five different job search sites. Implemented the user interface and collaborated with .NET developers to build back end requirements.

AFCOMPONENTS & UMAPPER // INTERACTIVE DEVELOPER (08.2007 - 12.2008)

Lead a website refresh of a flash component ecommerce site. Front end development on a Flex-based map-making application from alpha to beta phases. Used MVC patterns to develop Flash AS 3.0 components.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF FINE ARTS, MULTIMEDIA

Awarded 08.2006 from the University of Colorado at Denver.

SKILLS

DEVELOPMENT

ReactJS + Redux/Reflux, AngularJS 1&2, Backbone, JavaScript, ECMAScript 6, JQuery, Gulp, Grunt, SASS, PostCSS, Bootstrap, Mocha/Chai/Enzyme/Sinon, Wordpress, PHP, MySQL, NoSQL, Git, SVN, NPM.

SOFTWARE

Atom, Sublime Text, Coda, XCode, Photoshop, Sketch, Creative Suite, Atlassian tools, JIRA, Bamboo.